Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Afrika Bambaataa recordings
      - Jazzy sensation | Lessons 1-3, 1998; SR-20940; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & The Jazzy 5; Double Dee & Steinski (Box 162)
        Catalog # TB 466; A-side Matrix # TB 466A
      - EP III, 1995; SR-20941; Bassbin Twins (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20940. Different discsAnnotated
        Catalog # BBT 03; A-side Matrix # BBT-3-A
        Bassbin Records
        San Francisco, California
      - Jazzy sensation (remix), 1985; SR-20942; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & The Jazzy 5; Kryptic Crew; Tina B (Box 162)
        Catalog # TB 821; A-side Matrix # TB-821-I BOOPIE #1
      - Jazzy sensation, 1981; SR-20943; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & The Jazzy 5; Kryptic Crew; Tina B (Box 162)
        First Tommy Boy release?
        Catalog # TB 821; A-side Matrix # TB-821-I
      - Jazzy sensation, 1983; SR-20944; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & The Jazzy 5 (Box 162)
        Catalog # ACD 137031; A-side Matrix # MPO MU ACD 137031 A
        Accord
        France
      - Jazzy sensation, 1981; SR-25203; Kryptic Krew; Tina B; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & The Jazzy 5 (Box 162)
        First record with Afrika Bambaataa listed as artist.
        Catalog # TB 812; A-side Matrix # TB-812-I
      - The light, 1988; SR-20945; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20946. Double album.
        Catalog # EMC 3545; A-side Matrix # BAM-1A ALL PRAISE DUE TO ALLAH EMC 3545 A-1U-1-1
      - Shout it out; Sho nuff funky, 1988; SR-20946; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20945. Double album.Double album or different discs?
        Catalog # 12BAM 1; A-side Matrix # 12BAM 1A-1J-1-1 B Shout it out
      - Shout it out, 1988; SR-20947; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20948. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # V-15385; A-side Matrix # F/W Herbie Jr. V-1-15385-X601500A1B-Z2
        Capitol Records
      - Shout it out, 1988; SR-20948; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20947. Multiple copies.
      - Kick out the jams, 1986; SR-20949; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        Catalog # 258 473-0; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 258473-0-A
      - The decade of darkness 1990-2000, 1991; SR-20950; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20951. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # DFC 57705; A-side Matrix # DFC 57705-A
      - The decade of darkness 1990-2000, 1991; SR-20951; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20950. Multiple copies.
      - Beware (the funk is everywhere), 1986; SR-20952; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20953. Multiple copies.Promo
        Catalog # TBLP 1008; A-side Matrix # TB-1008-A-RE HERBIE JR.
      - Beware (the funk is everywhere), 1986; SR-20953; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20952. Multiple copies.Promo
      - Reckless, 1988; SR-20954; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; UB40 (Box 162)
        Catalog # V-15379; A-side Matrix # V-1-15379-X601496 B/C-Z2 0 B-3 1185 Z2 205-0
      - Reckless (vocal wildstyle mix); Recklessly (the Soca chant Zouk mix), 1988; SR-20955; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; UB40 (Box 162)
        No entry in Discogs.
        Catalog #; A-side Matrix # 12 EM 41 A-1-1-1- What's up my brother Amad?
      - Kick out the jams, 1986; SR-20956; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20957. Multiple copies.Promo
        Catalog # TB 880; A-side Matrix # TB-880-PRO-A
      - Kick out the jams, 1986; SR-20957; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20956. Multiple copies.Promo
      - Reckless, 1988; SR-20958; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; UB40 (Box 162)
        Catalog # 12EMX 41; A-side Matrix # 12 EMX 41 A-1-1-1-
      - Reckless, 1988; SR-20959; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; UB40 (Box 162)
        Catalog # 12EM 41; A-side Matrix # 12 EM 41 A-1-1-1- What's up my brother Amad?
      - Reckless, 1988; SR-20960; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; UB40 (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20961. Different discs.
        Catalog # 12EMXS 41; A-side Matrix # 12 EMXS 41 A-2C-1-1-
      - Reckless, 1988; SR-20961; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; UB40 (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20960. Different discs.
        Catalog # 12EMXS 41; A-side Matrix # 12 EMXS 41 A-3C-1-1-
      - Funk you!, 1985; SR-20962; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20963. Multiple copies.Promo
        Catalog # TB 870; A-side Matrix # TB-870-A-RE
      - Funk you!, 1985; SR-20963; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20962. Multiple copies.Promo
      - Universal future funk vol. 1, 1998; SR-20964; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        Catalog # PR2; A-side Matrix # PR2-A-(RE)
      - Bambaataa's theme (assault on Precinct 13); Tension, 1986; SR-20965; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20966. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # TB 879; A-side Matrix # TB-879-A
      - Bambaataa's theme (assault on Precinct 13); Tension, 1986; SR-20966; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20965. Multiple copies.
      - Soca fever (rock it); Electro funk express, 1991; SR-20967; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20968. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # DFC 047; A-side Matrix # DFC 047-I
      - Soca fever (rock it); Electro funk express, 1991; SR-20968; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20967. Multiple copies.
      - Sho nuff funky (re-mix), 1988; SR-20969; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; Slug-Go (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20970. Different discs.
        Catalog # 12 2026016; A-side Matrix # 2026016-A 20-4-88 I AFRIKA
        Italy
      - Sho nuff funky (funking all night mix), 1988; SR-20970; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; Slug-Go (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20969. Different discs.
        Catalog # 12EMX 57; A-side Matrix # 12 EMX 57 A-1-1-1
      - Sho nuff funky (funking all night mix), 1988; SR-20971; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; Slug-Go (Box 162)
      - Sho nuff funky (re-mix), 1988; SR-21108; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; Slug-Go (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-21109. Different discs.
      - Sho nuff funky, 1988; SR-21109; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; Slug-Go (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-21108. Different discs.
        Catalog # 12 EM 57; A-side Matrix # 12 EM 57 A-1-1-1
      - Thy will "b" funk, 1992; SR-20972; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20973. Different discs.
        Catalog # PR 1; A-side Matrix # PR1 A RE 1
      - Thy will "b" funk, 1992; SR-20973; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20972. Different discs. Annotated. Promo
        Catalog # PR-2; A-side Matrix # PR 2 A
      - Zulu war chant, 1993; SR-20974; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone; DJ Fashion; G.L.O.B.E. (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20975. Multiple copies.Promo
        Catalog # PRO-7389-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7389-A
        Profile Records
      - Zulu war chant, 1993; SR-20975; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone; DJ Fashion; G.L.O.B.E. (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20974. Multiple copies.Promo
      - What's the name of this nation?...Zulu!, 1993; SR-20976; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        Catalog # PRO-7409-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7409-A
      - Shake shake (le zook), 1988; SR-20977; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        Catalog # TM 002; A-side Matrix # TM 002 A
        Nescafe
      - Shake, 1987; SR-20978; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20979. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # 609 264; A-side Matrix # 609264 A
        Ariola
      - Shake, 1987; SR-20979; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20978. Multiple copies.
      - Push Pt. 2, 2004; SR-20980; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        Catalog # PRM 0060; A-side Matrix # PRM-00062 A
      - World destruction (Meltdown remix), 1985; SR-20981; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone; Lydon, John (Box 163)
        Catalog # CEL 191; A-side Matrix # CEL-191-A
        Celluloid
      - Throw ya funky hands up, 1995; SR-20982; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        Catalog # PRO 74420; A-side Matrix # PRO-7442-0-A
      - Throw ya funky hands up, 1995; SR-21110; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        Catalog # PRO 7442-0DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7442-0-A
      - The wildstyle (remix), 1983; SR-20983; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20984. Different discs.
        Catalog # 12AP 2762; A-side Matrix # 12AP-2762A1
        Japan
      - The wildstyle, 1983; SR-20984; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20983. Different discs.
        Catalog # CEL 165; A-side Matrix # CEL-165-A-2
      - Everyday people - the breakbeat party album (disc one), 2004; SR-20985; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20986. Double album.
        Catalog # PRM 0004; A-side Matrix # PRM-00061 A
      - Everyday people - the breakbeat party album (disc two), 2004; SR-20986; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20985. Double album.
        Catalog # PRM 0004; A-side Matrix # PRM-00061 C
      - Warlocks and witches, computer chips, microchips and you (disc one), 1996; SR-20987; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20988;SR-20989;SR-20990. Double album; Multiple copies.
        Catalog # PRO-1464-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1464-1-A
      - Warlocks and witches, computer chips, microchips and you (disc two), 1996; SR-20988; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20987;SR-20989;SR-20990. Double album; Multiple copies.
        Catalog # PRO-1464-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-1464-1-C
      - Warlocks and witches, computer chips, microchips and you (disc one), 1996; SR-20989; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20987;SR-20988;SR-20990. Double album; Multiple copies.
      - Warlocks and witches, computer chips, microchips and you (disc two), 1996; SR-20990; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20987;SR-20988;SR-20989. Double album; Multiple copies.
      - World destruction, 1984; SR-20991; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone; Lydon, John (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20992. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # VS 743-12; A-side Matrix # VS 743-13 A
        Virgin
      - World destruction, 1984; SR-20992; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone; Lydon, John (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20991. Multiple copies.
      - Afrika Bambaataa presents Time Zone vs. DJ Dara, 1996; SR-20993; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone; DJ Dara (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20994. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # SM-9048-0; A-side Matrix # SM-9048-0-A
        Sm:)e Communications
      - Afrika Bambaataa presents Time Zone vs. DJ Dara, 1996; SR-20994; Afrika Bambaataa; Time Zone; DJ Dara (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20993. Multiple copies.
      - Zulu groove, 1983; SR-20995; Shango (Box 163)
        Catalog # CEL 163; A-side Matrix # CEL-163-A-2
      - Shango message, 1983; SR-20996; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20997. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # CEL 164; A-side Matrix # CEL-164-A-2
      - Shango message, 1983; SR-20997; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20996. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # CEL 164; A-side Matrix # CEL -164-A-2
      - U don't have to be a star, 1987; SR-20998; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20999. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # NS 5501; A-side Matrix # CEL-5501A
        Nova Scratch
      - U don't have to be a star, 1987; SR-20999; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-20998. Multiple copies.
      - You're the one, 1991; SR-21000; Shango; Funk Queen (Box 163)
        Catalog # 162 440 529-1 DJ; A-side Matrix # 162-440-529-1A-SP
        4th & Broadway
      - Shango message, 1983; SR-21001; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21002. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # CEL 164; A-side Matrix # CEL -164-A
      - Shango message, 1983; SR-21002; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21001. Multiple copies.
      - Thank you, 1984; SR-21003; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21004. Multiple copies.Promo
        Catalog # CEL 170; A-side Matrix # CEL-170-A
      - Thank you, 1984; SR-21004; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21003. Multiple copies.Promo
      - Shango funk theology, 1984; SR-21005; Shango (Box 163)
        Label slightly different from sr-20995
        Catalog # CELL 6100; A-side Matrix # CELL-6100-A
      - Zulu groove, 1983; SR-21006; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21007. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # CEL 163; A-side Matrix # CEL-163-A
      - Zulu groove, 1983; SR-21007; Shango (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21006. Multiple copies.
      - Agharta-the city of Shamballa (subterranean world), 1998; SR-21008; I.F.O.; Identified Flying Objects; Afrika Bambaataa; Westbam (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21009. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # 74321 60356; A-side Matrix # B814621-01 A1 MK
        Low Spirit Recordings
      - Agharta-the city of Shamballa (subterranean world), 1998; SR-21009; I.F.O.; Identified Flying Objects; Afrika Bambaataa; Westbam (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21008. Multiple copies.
      - Agharta-the city of Shamballa (technolectro pop mix), 1998; SR-21010; I.F.O.; Identified Flying Objects; Afrika Bambaataa; Westbam (Box 163)
        Catalog # 74321 62473 1; A-side Matrix # B816158-01 A1 MK
      - Agharta-the city of Shamballa, 1999; SR-21011; I.F.O.; Identified Flying Objects; Afrika Bambaataa; Westbam (Box 163)
        Catalog # 12Mute234; A-side Matrix # 12 MUTE 234-A1
        Mute
      - Agharta-the city of Shamballa, 1999; SR-21012; I.F.O.; Identified Flying Objects; Afrika Bambaataa; Westbam (Box 163)
        Catalog # L12Mute234; A-side Matrix # L12 MUTE 234-A1
      - Bell-e 2 bell-e, 1996; SR-21013; Khayan; Khayan & the New World Power; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa presents: Khayan & the New World Power (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21014. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # DFC 276; A-side Matrix # DFC-271-A
      - Bell-e 2 bell-e, 1996; SR-21014; Khayan; Khayan & the New World Power; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa presents: Khayan & the New World Power (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21013. Multiple copies.
      - You ask for the moon, 1999; SR-21015; Khayan; Khayan & the New World Power; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa presents: Khayan & the New World Power (Box 163)
        Catalog # DFC 1354; A-side Matrix # DFC 1354-A
      - Happy, 1995; SR-21016; Khayan; Khayan & the New World Power; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa presents: Khayan & the New World Power (Box 163)
        Catalog # DFC 264; A-side Matrix # DFC 264-A
      - Feel the vibe, 1994; SR-21017; Khayan; Khayan & the New World Power; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa presents: Khayan & the New World Power (Box 163)
        Catalog # DFC 231; A-side Matrix # DFC-231-A
      - International; Haddsch, 2002; SR-21018; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & Universal Zulu Nation; 2K (Box 163)
        Test pressing. Unlabeled except for handwriting on jacket "Afrika Bambaataa & 2-K"
        Catalog # MVR002/2002; A-side Matrix # B266843-01 A1 HI
        Mellowvibes Records
      - Throw your hands up; Crowd says rewind, 2000; SR-21019; Afrika Bambaataa; Zulu Nation; Zombie Nation (Box 163)
        Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog # ZOM BI; A-side Matrix # ZOM BI-A1
      - International Zulu Style; Haddsch 2 HipHop, 2002; SR-21020; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & Universal Zulu Nation; 2K; Yakuphan; Shaka Zulu King Lito (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21021. Multiple copies.
      - International Zulu Style; Haddsch 2 HipHop, 2002; SR-21021; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & Universal Zulu Nation; 2K; Yakuphan; Shaka Zulu King Lito (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21020. Multiple copies.
      - Afrika Bambaataa and the Universal Zulu Nation in conjunction with Music of Life presents Hip Hop/Funk/Dance Classics Volume 1, 1991; SR-21022; Cold Crush Brothers; Grand Wizzard Theodore; Fantastic Five; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        Catalog # SPOCK 3; A-side Matrix # STOCK-3-A
        Music of Life
      - Afrika Bambaataa and the Universal Zulu Nation in conjunction with Music of Life presents Hip Hop/Funk/Dance Classics Volume 2, 1992; SR-21023; Cold Crush Brothers; Grandmixer DST; DJ Red Alert; Jazzy Jay; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        Catalog # SPOCK 4; A-side Matrix # SPOCK-4-A1
      - Afrika Bambaataa and the Universal Zulu Nation in conjunction with Music of Life presents Hip Hop/Funk/Dance Classics Volume 3, 1993; SR-21024; Spoony Gee; Wanda Dee; Debbie Deb; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        Catalog # MOLLP 030; A-side Matrix # MOLLP030-1
      - Funky groove, 1986; SR-21025; Hardrock Soul Movement; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21026. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # UKHAN 2; A-side Matrix # UKHAN-2-A-1
        Streetwave
      - Funky groove, 1986; SR-21026; Hardrock Soul Movement; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21025. Multiple copies.
      - Jingle bells; Deck the halls, 1992; SR-21027; Grand Rapmasters; Afrika Bambaataa; M.C. Globe; Pow Wow (Box 163)
        Catalog # ESL-7055; A-side Matrix # ESL-7055A
        Essex Entertainment, Inc.
        Hackensack, New Jersey
      - It's yours, 1998; SR-21028; Horrid; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        Catalog # WS-334-1; A-side Matrix # HORRID SIDE A WS-334-A
        Watershed Music
        Baychester, New York
      - Street happiness, 1988; SR-21029; Avitabile, Enzo; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        Catalog # 14 2031896; A-side Matrix # 2031896-A-22-11-88 A E. AVITABILE
      - If 6 was 9, 1996; SR-21030; Axiom Funk; Collins, Bootsy; Afrika Bambaataa; Grandmixer DST; Islam, T.C. (Box 163)
        Catalog # PR12 7212; A-side Matrix # PR12-7212-1-A
        Axiom
      - Sun City, 1986; SR-21031; Artists United Against Apartheid; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21032. Different discs.
        Catalog # V-56013; A-side Matrix # V-1-56013-240717-Z1
        Manhattan Records
      - Sun City, 1986; SR-21032; Artists United Against Apartheid; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21031. Different discs.
        Catalog # V-56013; A-side Matrix # V-1-56013-240717-C-Z2
      - Ethnic, 1991; SR-21033; Chunguitos; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        Catalog # 056 1224866; A-side Matrix # 056-1224866 A IN3 DMM
        Madrid, Spain
      - 2kool4skool, 1999; SR-21034; Uberzone; Afrika Bambaataa and the Soul Sonic Force (Box 163)
        Catalog # coa77145; A-side Matrix # THE EXCHANGE-N LZ S-40419
        City of Angels
        Los Angeles, California
      - Hydraulic funk; Flash light; Party with you ;Hell yeah (Disc one), 1999; SR-21035; Hydraulic Funk; Afrika Bambaataa; Brown, Steven "Boogie"; Fowler, Fred "Hassan" (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21036. Double album.
        Catalog # HYDRO 02; A-side Matrix # HYDRO-02A
        Bambaataa Music
      - Hydraulic funk; Flash light; Party with you ;Hell yeah (Disc two), 1999; SR-21036; Hydraulic Funk; Afrika Bambaataa; Brown, Steven "Boogie"; Fowler, Fred "Hassan" (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21035. Double album.
        Catalog # HYDRO 02; A-side Matrix # HYDRO-02C
      - The star spangled banner; The spell of Kingu, 2000; SR-21037; Hydraulic Funk; Afrika Bambaataa; Brown, Steven "Boogie"; Key, Francis Scott (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21038. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # PR 1206; A-side Matrix # PR 1206-A
      - The star spangled banner; The spell of Kingu, 2000; SR-21038; Hydraulic Funk; Afrika Bambaataa; Brown, Steven "Boogie"; Key, Francis Scott (Box 163)
        In same jacket as # SR-21037. Multiple copies.
      - Funky weekend, 1997; SR-21039; Express of sound; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 163)
        Catalog # MTR 2055; A-side Matrix # MTR 2055 A
      - Ndodemnyama (free South Africa), 1990; SR-21040; Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21041. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # WAR-067; A-side Matrix # WAR 067A
        Warlock Records
      - Ndodemnyama (free South Africa), 1990; SR-21041; Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21040. Multiple copies.
      - Universal future funk vol. 1, 1998; SR-21042; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
        Test pressing
        Catalog # PR2; A-side Matrix # PR-2A-1 RE
      - Funk you!, 1985; SR-21043; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21044. Multiple copies.Test pressing
      - Funk you!, 1985; SR-21044; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21043. Multiple copies.Test pressing
      - Ndodemnyama (free South Africa), 1990; SR-21045; Hip Hop Artists Against Apartheid; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # WAR 067; A-side Matrix # WAR 067A F/W CSB
      - Beware (the funk is everywhere), 1986; SR-21046; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
        Test pressing. Renegades of rhythm b-set
        Catalog # TB-1008-A; A-side Matrix # TB-1008-A
      - Who you funkin with?; What time is it?, 1985; SR-21047; Afrika Bambaataa and the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 164)
        Catalog # TB 865; A-side Matrix # TB-865-A
      - Power boy power; Save the world, 1992; SR-21048; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
      - Return to planet rock (the second coming), 1989; SR-21049; Afrika Bambaataa and the Soulsonic Force; Jungle Brothers (Box 164)
        Catalog # YR-768; A-side Matrix # YR-786-64LP-A
      - Bambaataa's theme (assault on Precinct 13); Tension, 1986; SR-21050; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
      - Zulu groove, 1983; SR-21051; Shango; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
      - Planet rock - the album, 1986; SR-21052; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 164)
        Catalog # TB 1007; A-side Matrix # TBLP-1007-A
      - Kick out the jams, 1986; SR-21053; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
      - Electro funk express, 1999; SR-21054; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family; Danmass (Box 164)
        Catalog # SPEC 130; A-side Matrix # SPEC 130-A1
      - Universal future funk vol. 1, 1998; SR-21055; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21056. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing
        Catalog # PR-2; A-side Matrix # PR2-A
      - Universal future funk vol. 1, 1998; SR-21056; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and Family (Box 164)
        In same jacket as # SR-21055. Multiple copies. Annotated. Test pressing